现在是第一个大型编码挑战的时候了
Now it's time for the first big coding challenge
在本课程中，让我们开始吧。
in this course, so let's get started.
现在，在我们开始真正的挑战之前，
Now, before we start with the actual challenge,
我想首先对文件结构进行一些更改
I want to first make some changes to the file structure
我们现在在这个项目中。
that we have in this project right now.
特别是，我想做什么
And in particular, what I want to do
就是把所有的图片放到一个文件夹里，
is to put all the images into one folder,
这样我就可以向您展示我们如何包含图像，
so that I can then show you how we can include the images,
像这样，当它们位于特定文件夹中时。
like this, when they are located in a specific folder.
所以现在他们都是，正如我们在这里看到的，
So right now they are all, as we can see here,
它们都在同一个、完全相同的文件夹中
they are all in the same, exact same folder
作为 index.html。
as the index.html.
这就是为什么我们要做的一切
And so that's why all we have to do
就是在这里声明名字，
is to declare the name here,
然后浏览器会找到它们
and the browser will then find them
基本上与 HTML 文档在同一个文件夹中。
basically in the same folder as the HTML document.
但是现在让我们通过点击这个图标来创建一个新文件夹，
But now let's create a new folder by clicking this icon,
我会称它为IMG，
and I'm gonna call it IMG,
然后我将把所有的图像放在那里。
and then I'm going to put all of the images there.
所以只是像这样拖放它们。
So just dragging and dropping them like this.
好的。
Okay.
所以现在如果我们重新加载页面，
And so now if we reload the page,
而不是这个，这是我们的演示，
and not this one, which is our demo,
但我们正在研究的那个。
but the one we're working on.
顺便说一句，这一次我不得不实际上
00:01:29,130​​ --> 00:01:31,200
手动重新加载页面，
And by the way, this time I had to actually
manually reload the page,
因为我在此期间关闭了计算机。
because I had my computer turned off in the meantime.
所以每当你这样做时，
And so whenever you do that,
第一次回来，
the very first time you come back,
您将不得不在此处手动重新加载页面，
you will have to manually reload the page here,
当您运行实时服务器扩展时。
when you are running the live server extension.
好的，请记住我们在上一个视频中安装了它，
Okay, so remember that we installed that in the last video,
所以如果我现在在这里做一些改变，
and so if I do some change here now,
那么这可能应该只是在之前工作。
then that should probably just work just before.
所以你看到有一些变化，它就出现了。
So you see there is some change, and there it appears.
但无论如何，你看，现在我们有
But anyway, you see that now that we have
这些图像在 IMG 文件夹中，
these images inside of the IMG folder,
它们不再与 index.html 位于同一文件夹中。
they are no longer found in the same folder as index.html.
所以这就是他们没有出现在这里的原因。
So that's why they don't appear up here.
所以我们需要在这里做的
So what we need to do here
是现在改变图像的路径，
is to change the path to the image now,
这不是一个难题。
and that's not a difficult problem.
我们所要做的就是开始新的道路
All we have to do is to start a new path
与文件夹的名称。
with the name of the folder.
这就是IMG。然后斜线，所以我们开始了。
So that's IMG. and then slash, and so here we go.
所以你看到图像现在再次出现在这里，在这个排水沟中。
So you see the image appears here now again, in this gutter.
所以让我们在这里做同样的事情，
And so let's do the same thing here,
给它一个保存，这是我们的图像。
give it a save, and here are our images back.
好的。
Okay.
所以通常我们总是将图像放在一个单独的文件夹中。
So usually we always put the images in a separate folder.
所以我认为向你展示这一点很重要，
And so I thought that was important to show you,
尤其是在这个挑战之前，
especially now before this challenge,
我们将在其中使用更多图像。
where we are going to use some more images.
所以关于挑战，在这里，
So about the challenge, and being here,
回到演示页面，
back in the demo page,
所以本质上我想让你做的
and so essentially what I want you to do
是在这里自己编写这部分代码。
is to code on your own this part here.
好吧，让我实际告诉你
All right, and let me actually show you
这应该在我们的标记中，所以在我们的 HTML 中，
where that should be in our markup, so in our HTML,
它就在文章之后。
and it is right here after the article.
好的？
Okay?
所以这个部分在这里关于相关的帖子
So this section here about the related posts
不再是文章的一部分。
is no longer part of the article.
它也不是页脚的一部分，
It's also not part of the footer,
所以在这里我们需要另一个元素。
and so here we will need another element.
而这个我实际上会为你写。
And this one I will actually write for you.
所以在这里我们将使用side元素，
So here we are going to use the aside element,
and the aside element is usually used
并且通常使用side元素
对于一些次要信息
for some secondary information
补充信息
that compliments the information
在页面的主要部分。
in the main part of the page.
所以在这种情况下，页面的主要部分是文章。
So in this case, the main part of the page is the article.
然后是旁白，这是次要信息
And then the aside, which is secondary information
基本上是一些相关的帖子
is basically some related posts
与文章相关的，所以主要部分。
that are related to the article, so to the main part.
好的？
Okay?
现在在视觉上很多时候我们使用了side元素
Now visually many times we use the aside element
作为侧边栏，
as a sidebar,
但不一定是这样。
but it doesn't have to be that way.
好的，但现在关于挑战本身。
Okay, but now about the challenge itself.
所以你看到它从这个标题开始。
So you see that it starts here with this heading.
所以你可以在这里试验哪个标题最好。
So you can experiment which heading is best here.
所以标题之一，H1，二，三，四，五，六，
So one of the headings, H1, two, three, four, five, and six,
记住，然后在这里你看到
remember, and then here you see
这实际上是一个列表，对吧？
that this is actually a list, right?
由于这些要点，您可以看到这一点。
You can see that because of these bullet points.
因此，对于这一部分，您可能应该使用一个列表。
And so here for this part, you should probably use a list.
现在，我们以前没有做的是拥有多个元素
Now, what we didn't do before was to have multiple elements
在一个列表项内。
inside of one list item.
所以在这里，例如，我们有列表项，
So up here, for example, we have the list item,
里面只有一些文字，
and in there there's only some text,
但你会看到，在每个项目中，都有一个图像，
but you see that here in each item, there is an image,
一个链接，然后在此处添加更多文本。
a link, and then some more texts here.
这完全没有问题。
And that's no problem at all.
所以在每个列表元素内部，
So inside of each list element,
可以有多个其他子元素，对吗？
there can be multiple other child elements, right?
有了这些信息，
And so with that information,
我认为您现在可以构建它。
I think you are now able to build this.
现在，最后，关于这里的图像，
Now, finally, just about the images here,
有些是您需要的信息。
that some are information that you need.
它们也在这个文件夹中，
They are also in this folder,
它们被称为related-1、2和3。
and they are called related-1, two, and three.
你要给它们的尺寸是 75 x 75 像素。
And the dimensions want you to give them is 75 by 75 pixels.
现在我想我给了你一切，
And now I think I gave you everything,
所以请现在暂停视频，
so please pause the video now,
花几分钟，10，15分钟，也许，
and take a couple of minutes, 10, 15 minutes maybe,
编写本节的 HTML。
to write up the HTML for this section.
祝你好运，一旦你准备好了，我会见到你的。
So good luck with that, and I'll see you once you're ready.
好的。
All right.
所以希望你做得很好。
So hopefully you did this just fine.
所以让我告诉你我是怎么做到的。
So let me show you how I did it.
我希望你开始看到它有多大帮助
And I hope that you start to see how helpful it is
VSCode 现在会自动关闭
that VSCode now automatically closes
我们的 HTML 元素，对吧？
our HTML elements, right?
所以这里的源码在IMG文件夹下，然后是related-1。
So the source here is in the IMG folder, and then related-1.
然后是替代文本，让我们说，
Then the alt text, let's just say,
这是一个人编程。
that this is a person programming.
当然，你的替代文字
And of course, your alt text
不必和我的完全一样。
doesn't have to be exactly the same as mine.
所以如果你的替代文字有点不同，
So if your alt text is a bit different,
这根本不是问题。
that is not a problem at all.
现在我们也需要关闭它。
And now we need to close it as well.
这就是图像部分。
And so that's the image part.
接下来，我们有一个超链接，所以一个锚标签，
Next, we have a hyperlink, so an anchor tag,
这里是href，这是我没有提到的，
and here the href, which is something that I didn't mention,
但希望你能明白，
but hopefully you figured it out,
这是链接之一
that this is one of the links
现在不应该指向任何地方。
that should not point anywhere for now.
那么如何学习Web开发。
So How to Learn Web Development.
现在终于有一些文字与作者那里，
And now finally there's some text with the author there,
所以我们可以为此使用一个段落。
and so we can use a paragraph for that.
所以由乔纳斯施梅特曼。
So by Jonas Schmedtmann.
好吧，给它一个保存。
Okay, giving it a save.
现在很好ely 格式，它应该出现在这里。
Now it's nicely formatted, and it should appear down here.
确实在这里。
And indeed here it is.
太好了，哦，实际上我只是在这里缺少标题。
Great, oh, I'm just missing here the heading actually.
所以让我回去，把那个
So let me go back, and put that
甚至在无序列表之前，所以我为此使用了 h4。
even before the unordered list, so I'm using an h4 for that.
但无论如何，让我们现在继续在这里建立我们的列表
But anyway, let's continue now building our list here
与下一个列表项。
with the next list item.
顺便说一句，如果你做了你的代码
And by the way, if you did your code
和我的有点不一样
a little bit different from mine,
这真的不是问题。
that's really not a problem.
这里重要的是你
What matters here is that you
尝试自己编写代码。
tried writing the code on your own.
这真的是最重要的
That is really the most important thing
我期待你在这里做的。
that I was expecting you to do here.
所以宽度为 75，高度也为 75。
So width of 75, the height also 75.
（按键）
(keys tapping)
再一次，一个链接指向无处。
Then again, a link pointing nowhere.
这个是 CSS 的未知力量，
And this one is The Unknown Powers of CSS,
和吉姆狄龙。
and by Jim Dillon.
我还不打算检查结果，
And I'm not going to check out the result just yet,
让我们完成它。
let's just finish it.
于是换了一张图。
So another image.
所以这部分的目标真的是
So the goal of this part here was really
让你基本上练习编写相同的代码，
to have you practice writing this same code basically,
或者一遍又一遍的非常相似的代码，
or very similar code over and over again,
因为这是唯一的方法
'cause this is the only way
这些东西真的会进入你的大脑。
that this stuff really gets into your brain.
所以让我们在屏幕上调用这个 JavaScript 代码，
So let's call this one JavaScript code on a screen,
再次，宽度为 75，高度为 75。
and again, the width of 75, and the height of 75.
你注意到我在写这个
And you notice I'm writing this
现在稍微快一点
a little bit faster right now,
因为我们不想浪费很多时间
because we don't want to waste a lot of time
写这个重复的代码。
writing this repetitive code.
这真的只是给你练习的，太棒了。
This was really just for you to practice, is awesome.
最后一段，
Finally the paragraph,
给它一个保存，美丽。
give it a save, and beautiful.
所以这看起来就像在我们的演示中一样，
So this looks just like in our demo,
我们现在拥有所有这些内容
and we have now all this content
我们想在这里显示
that we want to display here nicely marked up
以一种非常合乎逻辑的方式。
in a very logical way.
所以你可能想知道为什么我们使用
So you might be wondering why we used
在这种情况下，这里有一个列表。
a list here in this case.
以及这样做的原因
And the reason for that
基本上是语义HTML背后的想法，
is basically the idea behind Semantic HTML,
我之前解释过一点。
that I explained a little bit earlier.
因此，如果我们考虑这些相关的帖子，
So if we think about these related posts,
我们可以很容易地争论
we can very easily argue
它本质上是一个相关帖子的列表，对吗？
that it is essentially a list of related posts, right?
所以如果它是一个列表，我们应该在我们的 HTML 中标记它，
And so if it is a list, we should mark it up in our HTML,
所以我们应该把我们的 HTML 写成一个列表。
so we should write our HTML as a list.
这就是我们所做的。
And so that's just what we did.
稍后使用 CSS，我们将删除这些要点，
Later with CSS, we will then remove these bullet points,
因为它们在这种情况下没有多大意义，
because they don't make a lot of sense in this context,
但即使去掉了要点，
but even with the bullet points removed,
我们仍然想要这个元素的含义，
we still want a meaning of this element,
所以这里的所有这些都是一个列表。
So of all of this here to be a list.
但无论如何，这对这个视频来说已经足够了。
But anyway, that's enough for this video.
所以我真的希望你完成了这个挑战，
So I really hoped that you completed this challenge,
并且你喜欢这样做，即使需要一些时间，
and that you enjoyed doing it, even if it took some time,
即使你不得不复习一些概念
and even if you had to review some concepts
从以前的讲座。
from the previous lectures.
这完全正常，
That's completely normal,
这正是它实际上应该是的样子。
and that's exactly how it should be actually.
现在为了练得更均匀一点，
Now in order to practice a little bit more even,
还有另一个编码挑战即将到来，
there is another coding challenge coming up,
它完全脱离了这个项目，
which is completely detached from this project,
但这真的很令人兴奋。
but it's a really exciting one.
所以我希望很快能在那里见到你。
So I hope to see you there soon.